<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="sample_text">Some sample text</string>

    <!-- Categories -  Tab -->
    <string name="category_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="category_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_nightlife">Nightlife</string>

    <!--Food-->
    <string name="food_name_1">Jadka</string>
    <string name="food_address_1">Address: Rzeźnicza 24-25</string>
    <string name="food_short_info_1">Old Polish recipes.</string>
    <string name="food_long_info_1">We search old cookbooks to learn about the source of flavors that have been preserved in our collective memory. Old Polish recipes, messages about the cuisine of the old Wroclaw are interpreted in accordance with our experience and culinary schools that shaped us. In our kitchen we use products whose quality is determined by traditional methods of production, care for Polish heritage, respect for the wisdom of nature and craft practice. With great care we look at products and buy them only from hosts from Poland. To this we add what we ourselves pick up in the forest, orchard, in the meadow, in the garden, on the Oder. We focus on transforming raw nature into beautiful dishes using traditional food processing techniques.</string>

    <string name="food_name_2">Pod Papugami</string>
    <string name="food_address_2">Address: Sukiennice 9a</string>
    <string name="food_short_info_2">Restaurant and Cocktail Bar in the Old Town.</string>
    <string name="food_long_info_2">Wroclaw Market Square, Hollywood atmosphere, delicious cuisine, tempting bar and lots of good music ... Sounds like a recipe for a great restaurant. Under the parrots, it was not without reason that it became known as a cult place on the entertainment map of Wroclaw. And not only because of mezzanine ... Menu? It is a mix of the latest culinary trends, fresh, seasonal products and unrestrained fantasy of Mariola Monczak - our chef in the Mediterranean and French flavors.</string>

    <!-- Sights -->
    <string name="sights_name_1">The Old Town Hall</string>
    <string name="sights_address_1">Address: Rynek Ratusz 1</string>
    <string name="sights_short_info_1">The Old Town Hall is one of the main landmarks of the city.</string>
    <string name="sights_long_info_1">The Old Town Hall (Polish: Stary Ratusz) of Wrocław stands at the center of the city’s Market Square. The Gothic town hall built from the 13th century is one of the main landmarks of the city. The Old Town Hall has long history reflects developments that have taken place in the city since its initial construction. The town hall serves the city of Wroclaw and is used for civic and cultural events such as concerts held in its Great Hall. In addition, it houses a museum and a basement restaurant.</string>

    <string name="sights_name_2">Sky Tower</string>
    <string name="sights_address_2">Address: Powstańców Śląskich 95</string>
    <string name="sights_short_info_2">The tallest building in Poland with a publicly accessible viewpoint.</string>
    <string name="sights_long_info_2">Sky Tower is a skyscraper in Wrocław, Poland. Construction began in December 2007 with the demolition of the 24-story Poltegor structure, until then the tallest building in the city. Sky Tower is the tallest building in Poland in the category of height to roof and category of highest floor but shorter than the Palace of Culture and Science architecturally. On the 49th floor is a publicly accessible viewpoint.</string>

    <!-- Culture -->
    <string name="culture_name_1">Capitol Theater</string>
    <string name="culture_address_1">Address: Piłsudskiego 67</string>
    <string name="culture_short_info_1">Theater open to musical and theatrical forms.</string>
    <string name="culture_long_info_1">Capitol is a theater open to revealing musical and theatrical forms, but it does not turn away from good traditions. He exhibits performances for adults and children: from entertainment performances, Broadway musicals to adaptations of Polish and world literature, engaging audiences in an intelligent dialogue with artists. He proves that in contemporary musical theater not only entertainment is possible, but also bold reflection on difficult, sometimes controversial matters - private and public.</string>

    <string name="culture_name_2">The National Forum of Music</string>
    <string name="culture_address_2">Address: Plac Wolności 1</string>
    <string name="culture_short_info_2">Institution whose main aim is to encourage active participation in cultural life.</string>
    <string name="culture_long_info_2">The National Forum of Music is the City of Wrocław institution of culture, co-governed by the Minister of Culture and National Heritage, the Community of Wrocław and the Lower Silesian Province. The National Forum of Music operates the state-of-the-art multifunctional concert venue of the same name located in the historic centre of Wrocław. This performing arts organization was established on 22 May 2014 through merging the International Festival Wratislavia Cantans and the Wrocław Philharmonic. Andrzej Kosendiak, director of the NFM, has been one of the proponents and authors the new performing arts organization and the new venue. </string>

    <!-- Nightlife -->
    <string name="nightlife_name_1">Incognito</string>
    <string name="nightlife_address_1">Address: Plac Solny 11</string>
    <string name="nightlife_short_info_1">Incognito Cocktail Bar</string>
    <string name="nightlife_long_info_1">Speakeasy (hidden in a restaurant) hidden in the Bistro Garage. We offer a private atmosphere and professional bartending and waiter service. A great place to meet in a narrow circle of friends and spend time in a cozy atmosphere.</string>

    <string name="nightlife_name_2">X-Demon</string>
    <string name="nightlife_address_2">Address: Plac Wolności 7</string>
    <string name="nightlife_short_info_2">Nightclub - HOUSE / DANCE and RnB</string>
    <string name="nightlife_long_info_2">A modern entertainment center, created for the most demanding and thirsty for the best clubbing at a high level. Two entirely different music areas (HOUSE / DANCE and RnB). X-Demon is a well-known brand especially in Zielona Góra and Leszno, where two clubs from this network are located. From now, also in the capital of Lower Silesia ...</string>

</resources>
